kgb.com 2013-11-22

# kgbdeals

The websites located at kgb.com, kgbdeals.com, thedealist.com and sowhatsthedeal.com (each, a "kgb Website") are operated by kgb Deals, Inc. and its subsidiaries ("kgb" or "we" or "our" or "us". Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information collected from you ("User" or "you" or "your"), what we do with it, with whom we share it, and how you can correct or change such information. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy carefully, especially before providing any personal data through the Service or the kgb Website. By visiting the kgb Website or using any of the services available on the kgb Website (collectively, the "Service"), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of personal information about you as described in this Privacy Policy and as may be directed by you on the Site.

The kgb Website is operated in and controlled from the United States of America. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the kgb Website, or if you wish to unsubscribe from the Service (or any other services) on the kgb Website for which you have previously registered, please click [here](http://www.kgbdeals.com/company/contact) to go to our Contact Us form. This Privacy Policy, your use of the kgb Website or the Service, and any dispute related to use of personal information provided to us, is subject to the then-current version of the kgbdeals Terms of Service. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, all terms shall have the meaning defined in the kgbdeals Terms of Service.

### WE ENCOURAGE YOU TO READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE SERVICE OR THE KGB WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE kgbdeals TERMS OF SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, PLEASE EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SERVICE OR THE KGB WEBSITE.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it regularly. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, and/or by means of a notice on our home page.

The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the kgb Website. Your continued use of the Service and/or the kgb Website after such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

### Protecting the Privacy of Minors

Minors under the age of 18 may not use the Service or the kgb Website. By accessing and/or using the Service or the kgb Website you are representing that you are at least 18 years of age and that you have the permission of your parent or guardian to use the Service and the kgb Website. We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known to be under the age of 18. If we obtain actual knowledge that a User is under the age of 18, we will take steps to remove that User's Personal Information from our records. kgb does not sell products for purchase by children, nor is any part of the kgb Website intentionally designed to attract the attention of anyone under the age of 18, however, we may offer Vouchers for children's products with the intention that they will be purchased by adults. If you are under 18, you must obtain the permission of a parent or guardian before submitting information in connection with the Service and the kgb Website.

### Types of Information We Collect

#### Personal Information

If you create an account and join kgbdeals in order to take advantage of the full range of services offered on the kgb Website, we ask for and record some Personal Information. "Personal Information" means information you knowingly choose to disclose to us that contains details about the identity of the User, and includes your name, email address, mailing information, and country/region. We will use your email address to send you a daily email announcing the Voucher or Vouchers to be offered for that particular day. We may also use your email address to send you updates and news about the kgb Website. We may use your mailing information to effectuate online transactions on the kgbdeals Website or in connection with the Service.

When you purchase a Voucher, you will need to submit your credit card number and other payment information so that our third-party service providers can process your payment for the Voucher. Such credit card and payment account information is also considered Personal Information. 

#### Contributions

We store and may publicly display your contributions to the kgb Website in order to provide and enhance the services that we offer. When we display your contributions, we may do so together with your user name. "Contributions" refers to any content you submit or post to the kgb Website for public display, such as ratings, restaurant or spa reviews, comments, photos, facts, and other similar types of information. Please do not include information in your contributions that you expect to be kept private or that may infringe on the rights of any third parties.

#### Feedback

If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any Personal Information and other content you provide in your communication so we can effectively respond to your communication.

#### Activity

We automatically record information relating to your use of the Service via the kgb Website (through the use of electronic tools such as cookies, web beacons or pixel tags), such as the searches you undertake, the pages you visit, your browser or phone type, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, requested Uniform Resource Locator ("URL"), referring URL, and timestamp information, and other similar types of information. We use this information to operate administer, and troubleshoot the kgb Website, analyze trends, gather demographic information, and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We may also share this information with our kgbdeals Merchants, service providers and advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming.

### Cookies and Other Navigational Tools

To enhance your experience with the kgb Website, we store cookies on your computer and we may use Web beacons or pixel tags. Pixel tags and web beacons are graphic images placed on certain pages on our kgb Website or in our emails to you that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies also allow us to collect non-personal information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on. Cookies, pixel tags and web beacons, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other Personal Information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering for the Service on the kgb Website. However, once you choose to furnish the kgb Website with Personal Information, this Personal Information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the kgb Website. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at the kgb Website (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to the kgb Website), and to save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. In addition, we may use third party advertising companies to display advertisements on the kgb Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by the kgb Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline some or all cookies if you prefer. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the kgb Website may not work properly or at all.

#### Facebook Connect

The kgb Website allows users to access Facebook Connect to interact with friends and to share on Facebook through Wall and friends' News Feeds. If you are logged into kgbdeals and Facebook, when you click on "Connect with Facebook" your profiles will merge if the email addresses match. If the email addresses don't match, we ask you if you want to merge them and you must enter your kgbdeals password to validate that they control that account. If you are already logged into kgbdeals but not logged into Facebook, when you click on "Connect with Facebook" you will be prompted to enter your Facebook credentials or to "Sign up for Facebook." By proceeding you are allowing the kgb Website to access your information and you are agreeing to the Facebook Terms of Use in your use of the kgb Website.

Conversely, if you are not currently registered as a kgbdeals User and you click on "Sign in Using Facebook," you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials and then be given the option to register and join kgbdeals. Once you register on the kgb Website and Connect with Facebook, you will be able to automatically post recent activity back to Facebook. You have the option to disable Facebook Connect at any time by logging into "My Profile" and clicking on "My Facebook Profile." Further, you can edit privacy settings for the reviews that appear on Facebook or disconnect this service by visiting the Facebook Application Settings page.

### How We Use Your Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about the Service, and to offer you other products, programs, or services we believe may be of interest to you. We may also use your Personal Information to administer sweepstakes and contests.

We may also share your information with third parties as described below.

We use information about which links have been followed and whether action has been taken on another party's website to improve our offerings and to customize the Service.

Technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, IP address, pages visited, and average time spent on our the kgb Website, may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our website design and functionality.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the kgb Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to the kgb Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you choose to use the separate products or services offered by such third-party advertising companies, disclose information to the providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policy. You should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their products or services.

### Release of Your Information to Third Parties

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we generally do not sell, trade, rent or share Personal Information that we collect with third parties unless we have your consent to do so.

We may share your information when required to do so. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights.

We may use or disclose your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena, or other similar governmental request we may receive.

If we believe it is necessary, we may disclose your Personal Information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (i) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (ii) investigate, enforce or apply our kgb Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy; (iii) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or (iv) protect our rights, reputation, or property or that of our Service, Users, affiliates, third parties, or the public. 

We may share your information with authorized third party service providers. Under the circumstances identified below, we may share your Personal Information with third parties.

We may also disclose your information to particular third party kgbdeals Merchants who, as part of the offer, request information on kgb customers who purchased a Voucher offered by such Merchant. _In_ those cases, we may share some of your Personal Information as well as your non-personal activity information with kgbdeals Merchants. Sharing this information will allow a kgbdeals Merchant to market directly to you should they choose to do so. Please note that we will only provide a kgbdeals Merchant your information with an opt-in notice to you, in which you will have a chance to choose that kgb not give the kgbdeals Merchant your Personal Information. We specifically disclaim any responsibility or liability for the actions of such kgbdeals Merchant. While we inform them that they are only permitted to communicate with you for the purposes of the specific promotion with kgb, we do not have any responsibility for the actions of the kgbdeals Merchant, and the actions of the kgbdeals Merchant are not in our control.

We may provide some of our services and products through third parties. These third-party service providers perform certain administrative and promotional functions on our behalf, including, but not limited to, sending out our daily emails. We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the kgb Website. We may share your Personal Information with such service providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal or email, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the kgb Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for advertisers. Please note that this is not Personal Information, only general summaries of the activities of our Users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us.

We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies with whom we have business relationships and may have to also share their information with service providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. We encourage kgb Merchants and third-party service providers and advertising companies to adopt and post their own privacy policies. However, the use of your Personal Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control.

We may share your information in a business transfer. We may transfer your information to a third party in connection with a sale or acquisition of kgb or substantially all of its assets (or a merger of kgb with another company). If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personal Information. 

### Security of Your Personal Information

While this Privacy Policy expresses kgb's standards for maintenance of Personal Information, kgb is not in a position to guarantee the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in unintentional disclosure of your Personal Information. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. But no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage, is 100 percent secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Updating and Correcting Your Personal Information

We believe that you should have the ability to access and edit the Personal Information you provide us. You may change any of your Personal Information by clicking [here](http://www.kgbdeals.com/company/contact) go to our Contact Us form. Please indicate your name, address and email address, and what information you would like to update when you contact us.

We encourage you to promptly update your Personal Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on the kgb Website. In addition, it may be impossible for us to completely delete all of your information, even if you terminate your account or unsubscribe from the Service, because we periodically backup information.

### Notice of Privacy Rights to California Residents

California law allows users of this Website that reside in California to know the third parties with whom we shared their Personal Information for those third parties' own direct marketing purposes. The type of information and instances in which we share such information is detailed in this Privacy Policy. However, if you are a resident of California and you would like to know the names and addresses of the specific third parties with whom we shared your Personal Information for their own direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the categories of the Personal Information we shared, you should click [here](http://www.kgbdeals.com/company/contact) to go our Contact Us form. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Personal Information you do not want us to share with third parties. The request should be sent to the attention of our legal department, and labeled "California Customer Choice Notice." Alternatively, you may send us a written request for such information to the address set forth below. Please allow 30 days for a response.

### Notice of Privacy Rights to International Users

We collect, process, store, disclose and dispose of Personal Information that you submit to the Service or the kgb Website in accordance with applicable United States law. Please note that the Personal Information you submit to the Service or the kgb Website will be transferred to the United States to be processed by us in order to provide the Service to you or for such other purposes as set forth in this Privacy Policy. By choosing to voluntarily submit Personal Information to the Service or the kgb Website, you are consenting to the transfer of such Personal Information to the United States. Please be aware that United States law may offer different levels of protection for Personal Information than may be available in your country.

### How to Reach Us

If you wish to contact us on matters or disputes related to this policy, or any other matter or dispute related to the Service (including customer service inquiries), you can reach us using the contact details set forth below:

kgb deals, Inc.  
655 Madison Ave.  
3d Floor  
New York, New York 10065  
Click [here](http://www.kgbdeals.com/company/contact) to go to our Contact Us form.

### Disputes

Any dispute related to this Privacy Policy, the kgb Website or the Service must be submitted to arbitration and Users of the kgb Website and/or the Service must bring any claims in their individual capacity, and not as a plaintiff or class member in any purported class or representative proceeding.

### Sole Statement

The foregoing statements, terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy represent the sole statement of our privacy policy, and no summary or other version, or other policy, in any form, including, without limitation, machine-generated, is valid.

This Privacy Policy was last modified on October 19, 2011 and is effective immediately.
